{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "targetLocation": "US", "language": "en", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "topic": ["topic1", "topic2"], "dateScraped": 1585864570.663757, "questionOriginal": "<a href=\"example.com/dir1\">What is COVID-19?</a>", "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerOriginal": "<p><a href=\"example.com/dir2\">Coronaviruses</a> are a large family of viruses.</p>", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "questionUUID": "c377c134-752c-11ea-bba6-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c377c242-752c-11ea-b9ba-9801a78e188f", "ID": "example|||2435204608278536658", "answerContainsURLs": false, "answerToks2URL": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "targetLocation": "US", "language": "en", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "topic": ["topic1", "topic2"], "dateScraped": 1585864570.9373498, "questionOriginal": "<a href=\"example.com/dir1\">What is COVID-19?</a>", "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerOriginal": "<p><a href=\"example.com/dir2\">Coronaviruses</a> are a large family of viruses.</p>", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "questionUUID": "c3a1806e-752c-11ea-95c7-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c3a18190-752c-11ea-bd27-9801a78e188f", "ID": "example|||2435204608278536658", "answerContainsURLs": false, "answerToks2URL": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "targetLocation": "US", "language": "en", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "topic": ["topic1", "topic2"], "dateScraped": 1585864571.212103, "questionOriginal": "<a href=\"example.com/dir1\">What is COVID-19?</a>", "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerOriginal": "<p><a href=\"example.com/dir2\">Coronaviruses</a> are a large family of viruses.</p>", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "questionUUID": "c3cb6cf8-752c-11ea-a941-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c3cb6e10-752c-11ea-b472-9801a78e188f", "ID": "example|||2435204608278536658", "answerContainsURLs": false, "answerToks2URL": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "targetLocation": "US", "language": "en", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "topic": ["topic1", "topic2"], "dateScraped": 1585864571.488447, "questionOriginal": "<a href=\"example.com/dir1\">What is COVID-19?</a>", "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerOriginal": "<p><a href=\"example.com/dir2\">Coronaviruses</a> are a large family of viruses.</p>", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "questionUUID": "c3f597a8-752c-11ea-8b54-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c3f598de-752c-11ea-b513-9801a78e188f", "ID": "example|||2435204608278536658", "answerContainsURLs": false, "answerToks2URL": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "targetLocation": "US", "language": "en", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "topic": ["topic1", "topic2"], "dateScraped": 1585864571.7780962, "questionOriginal": "<a href=\"example.com/dir1\">What is COVID-19?</a>", "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerOriginal": "<p><a href=\"example.com/dir2\">Coronaviruses</a> are a large family of viruses.</p>", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "questionUUID": "c421ca12-752c-11ea-80c9-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c421cb1e-752c-11ea-8d41-9801a78e188f", "ID": "example|||2435204608278536658", "answerContainsURLs": false, "answerToks2URL": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "targetLocation": "US", "language": "en", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "topic": ["topic1", "topic2"], "dateScraped": 1585864572.052607, "questionOriginal": "<a href=\"example.com/dir1\">What is COVID-19?</a>", "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerOriginal": "<p><a href=\"example.com/dir2\">Coronaviruses</a> are a large family of viruses.</p>", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "questionUUID": "c44bad3a-752c-11ea-8186-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c44bae74-752c-11ea-b02f-9801a78e188f", "ID": "example|||2435204608278536658", "answerContainsURLs": false, "answerToks2URL": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "targetLocation": "US", "language": "en", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "topic": ["topic1", "topic2"], "dateScraped": 1585864572.357572, "questionOriginal": "<a href=\"example.com/dir1\">What is COVID-19?</a>", "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerOriginal": "<p><a href=\"example.com/dir2\">Coronaviruses</a> are a large family of viruses.</p>", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "questionUUID": "c47a35ee-752c-11ea-8fa5-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c47a3724-752c-11ea-9ed7-9801a78e188f", "ID": "example|||2435204608278536658", "answerContainsURLs": false, "answerToks2URL": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "targetLocation": "US", "language": "en", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "topic": ["topic1", "topic2"], "dateScraped": 1585864572.6319308, "questionOriginal": "<a href=\"example.com/dir1\">What is COVID-19?</a>", "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerOriginal": "<p><a href=\"example.com/dir2\">Coronaviruses</a> are a large family of viruses.</p>", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "questionUUID": "c4a41300-752c-11ea-aab6-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c4a41418-752c-11ea-966d-9801a78e188f", "ID": "example|||2435204608278536658", "answerContainsURLs": false, "answerToks2URL": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "targetLocation": "US", "language": "en", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "topic": ["topic1", "topic2"], "dateScraped": 1585864572.902952, "questionOriginal": "<a href=\"example.com/dir1\">What is COVID-19?</a>", "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerOriginal": "<p><a href=\"example.com/dir2\">Coronaviruses</a> are a large family of viruses.</p>", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "questionUUID": "c4cd6dcc-752c-11ea-902a-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c4cd6eda-752c-11ea-a986-9801a78e188f", "ID": "example|||2435204608278536658", "answerContainsURLs": false, "answerToks2URL": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "targetLocation": "US", "language": "en", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "topic": ["topic1", "topic2"], "dateScraped": 1585864573.187022, "questionOriginal": "<a href=\"example.com/dir1\">What is COVID-19?</a>", "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerOriginal": "<p><a href=\"example.com/dir2\">Coronaviruses</a> are a large family of viruses.</p>", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "questionUUID": "c4f8c65c-752c-11ea-858f-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c4f8c7b0-752c-11ea-9f4b-9801a78e188f", "ID": "example|||2435204608278536658", "answerContainsURLs": false, "answerToks2URL": {}}
